SO, NOW, WHAT
IS THIS NOW?
GOOGILY WORM.
( giggles )
AND THIS?
GLOW POP JIGGLY JAMMER.
( laughs )
BAIT IS SO FUNNY.
HEY, UM, WHAT'S THIS?
OH, A HUNK OF SANDWICH
FROM LAST YEAR.
OH, GELLER'S GOT ONE HOOKED.
OH! LOOKS LIKE A BIG ONE!
UH-OH, IT'S THE CLASSIC STRUGGLE
BETWEEN MAN AND...
SOMEONE KNOCKED OVER A LAMP.
HEY, YOU GUYS, YOU KNOW
WHAT'S GOING TO BE GREAT
ABOUT THE FISHING TRIP
THIS YEAR?
WHEN MY DAD
GIVES ME THAT
"JOEY, WHAT ARE
YOU DOING WITH
YOUR LIFE?" STUFF
I CAN SAY, "WELL,
I'M DOING A MOVIE
"WITH CHARLTON
HESTON, DAD.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING
WITH YOUR LIFE?"
( quacking )
YOU DON'T HAVE TO STOP HAVING
FUN JUST BECAUSE I'M HERE.
KATHY DIDN'T CHEAT
ON ALL OF YOU.
WELL, EXCEPT YOU.
( quacking )
Monica:
HEY, JOEY, I DON'T THINK
YOU SHOULD LEAVE CHANDLER ALONE.
IT'S ONLY BEEN TWO DAYS
SINCE HE BROKE UP
WITH KATHY.
MAYBE YOU CAN GO
FISHING NEXT WEEK.
THERE'S NOTHING I
CAN DO FOR HIM NOW.
HE'S STILL IN
HIS SWEAT PANTS.
THAT'S ONLY PHASE ONE.
YOU KNOW,
I'LL BE BACK
FOR PHASE TWO.
I WOULD NEVER
MISS PHASE TWO.
WHAT'S PHASE TWO?
GETTING DRUNK AND
GOING TO A STRIP CLUB.
HOW DOES GOING
TO A STRIP CLUB
MAKE HIM BETTER?
THERE ARE NAKED LADIES THERE.
IT HELPS HIM GET
TO PHASE THREE:
"PICTURING YOURSELF
WITH OTHER WOMEN."
THERE ARE NAKED LADIES
THERE, TOO.
YEAH.
( quacking )
WOULD YOU GIVE ME
ONE MINUTE, PLEASE?
♪ SO NO ONE TOLD YOU
LIFE WAS GONNA BE THIS WAY ♪
♪ YOUR JOB'S A JOKE,
YOU'RE BROKE ♪
♪ YOUR LOVE LIFE'S D.O.A. ♪
♪ IT'S LIKE YOU'RE ALWAYS
STUCK IN SECOND GEAR ♪
♪ WHEN IT HASN'T BEEN YOUR DAY ♪
♪ YOUR WEEK, YOUR MONTH,
OR EVEN YOUR YEAR ♪
♪ BUT I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ WHEN THE RAIN
STARTS TO POUR ♪
♪ I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ LIKE I'VE BEEN THERE BEFORE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE THERE
FOR ME, TOO. ♪
THESE WILL MATCH THE JACKET
YOU PICKED OUT FOR ME?
MM-HMM.
THERE WE GO.
THERE IT IS.
OH, YOU KNOW WHAT I NEED?
YEAH?
GLOVES.
BROWN LEATHER DRESS GLOVES.
OH, OKAY, UH,
WELL, LET'S SEE.
YOU'RE ABOUT A, WELL
THIS ONE IS LARGE.
AND, UH, THIS ONE...
ALSO LARGE?
YEAH. OKAY.
TWO LARGES COMING RIGHT UP.
OKAY.
( scoffs )
RACHEL, COULD I HAVE A MOMENT?
YES.
I WAS WONDERING...
MY NIECE, YOU SEE,
IS IN TOWN FROM LONDON.
SHROPSHIRE, REALLY,
BUT YOU KNOW...
WELL, SHE'S ABOUT YOUR AGE,
I'D SAY.
ANYWAY, I HAVE TICKETS
FOR THE OPERA, DIE FLEDERMAUS
AND I WAS WONDERING
IF YOU WOULD LIKE
TO KEEP HER COMPANY
THIS EVENING.
SURE, YOU GOT IT.
GREAT. COUNT ME IN.
ME, FLEDERMAUS, GREAT.
I REALLY...
HMM? OH, YES, OF COURSE.
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU
SO VERY MUCH.
SO?
GLOVES?
OH, RIGHT, I'LL
BE RIGHT BACK.
ACTUALLY,
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I KIND OF...
I GOT TO TAKE OFF
BUT I WAS CURIOUS...
DO YOU HAVE ANY
PLANS FOR TONIGHT?
NO. NOTHING!
I INVESTED IN THIS NIGHTCLUB
AND IT'S OPENING TONIGHT.
YEAH, THAT WOULD BE GREAT.
YOU'RE INTO HARD-CORE
S&M, RIGHT?
WELL, I-I GU... I GUE...
I'M KIDDING.
( chuckles )
WHEW!
I GOT TO GET
THERE EARLY
BUT I'M GOING
TO PUT YOU ON
THE V.I.P. LIST.
LOOK FOR ME.
YEAH. GREAT.
I'LL SEE YOU TONIGHT.
OKAY.
I ALMOST FORGOT THE
TICKETS, DIDN'T I?
WHAT?
FOR YOU AND EMILY.
TONIGHT.
DIE FLEDERMAUS.
OH... OH, RIGHT.
I THINK
YOU'LL LIKE IT.
IT HAS TWO OUT OF
THE THREE TENORS.
OH, YAY!
YOU KNOW, I CAN'T BELIEVE
KATHY DID THIS TO ME.
I REALLY THOUGHT
THAT SHE WAS THE ONE.
WELL, I'LL TELL YOU WHAT.
FROM NOW ON, I'M NOT GETTING
OUT OF THIS CHAIR EVER, OKAY?
FROM NOW ON,
THIS CHAIR IS "THE ONE."
YOU KNOW WHAT ELSE
IS "THE ONE"?
MY SWEAT PANTS.
COME ON, MAN
JUST-JUST TAKE THE
SWEATS OFF, OKAY?
JUST TAKE 'EM OFF,
AND WE'LL HAVE SOME FUN.
HEY, HEY.
HI.
HAVE A GOOD TIME?
CATCH A BIG ONE?
OH, GOD,
YOU GUYS HAVE NO IDEA.
WOW, YOU STINK!
ARE YOU KIDDING?
YEAH, THREE DAYS ON THE LAKE
WITHOUT A SHOWER.
PLUS, I FELL INTO THAT BIG
TUB OF WORMS AT THE BAIT STAND.
HEY, H-HOW'S HE DOING?
HE HASN'T MOVED IN TWO DAYS.
HEY, BUDDY, HOW'S IT GOING?
HEY, YOU SEE THAT?
HE JUST NEEDED HIS PAL
TO COME HOME.
ALL RIGHT, I GOT TO
GO MEMORIZE MY LINES.
ME AND CHARLTON HESTON,
BRIGHT AND EARLY TOMORROW, BABY!
YEAH, YOU DO 'EM!
HEY.
Ross:
Phoebe:
HEY, MONICA.
UH-OH, WHAT'S THE MATTER?
OH, IT'S...
JOSHUA INVITED ME
TO THIS FANCY CLUB
OPENING TONIGHT.
OOH, BUT I ALREADY
TOLD MR. WALTHAM
THAT I WOULD
TAKE HIS NIECE
TO THE DUMB
OLD OPERA, SO...
WHAT ARE YOU
GOING TO DO?
( sighs )
I DON'T KNOW, SWEETIE.
NO! HELP ME!
I CAN'T.
I HAVE TO WORK.
PHOEBE...?
I WOULD, BUT I GET
MORNING SICKNESS IN THE EVENING.
UNLESS... SHE WANTS
TO SPEND THE NIGHT
HOLDING MY HAIR BACK FOR ME.
OH, GOSH, YOU GUYS, COME ON.
THIS IS... I HAVE
TO MEET JOSHUA.
THIS IS MY ONE CHANCE
FOR HIM TO SEE THE FUN RACHEL.
YOU KNOW,
THE WOULDN'T-IT-BE-GREAT-
IF-SHE-WERE-MY-WIFE RACHEL?
OH, ALL RIGHT.
ARE JOEY AND CHANDLER BACK?
CHANDLER'S STILL IN PHASE ONE
AND JOEY'S
THAT THING YOU SMELL.
OH, THAT'S...
HI.
SO...?
NO.
OH, COME ON.
( knocking )
BET SHE'S HERE.
NO, WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
ROSS, PLEASE!
YOU WANT ME TO TAKE SOME GIRL
I'VE NEVER MET TO THE OPERA
SO YOU CAN GO TO A CLUB
AND FLIRT WITH SOME GUY? HMM.
YEAH, THAT-THAT IS A TOUGHIE...
OH, SHE'S LOOKING
DOWN THE HALL.
( gasps )
SHE LOOKED RIGHT AT ME.
OH, WAIT, YOU CAN'T SEE PEOPLE
THROUGH THAT LITTLE HOLE
CAN YOU?
HELLO?
Woman:
( shrieks )
OH, I'LL BE RIGHT THERE.
OKAY, ROSS,
PLEASE COME ON.
I THOUGHT WE HAD MOVED ON.
I THOUGHT WE HAD GOTTEN
TO A PLACE
WHERE WE COULD BE HAPPY
FOR EACH OTHER.
WAS THAT JUST ME?
ALL RIGHT, I'LL DO IT.
OH, THANK YOU.
THANK YOU, THANK YOU,
THANK YOU!
EMILY?
OH, YES.
I'M RACHEL GREEN.
THANK GOODNESS.
YEAH.
THERE'S BEEN A TEENY,
TEENY CHANGE OF PLANS.
TURNS OUT I'M NOT
FREE TONIGHT, SO...
REALLY? WELL,
THAT'S JUST LOVELY, ISN'T IT?
I MUST HAVE MISSED YOUR CALL
EVEN THOUGH I DIDN'T
LEAVE THE FLAT ALL DAY.
OH, WELL, NO, I...
NO, NO, NO,
THAT'S NOT RUDE.
IT'S PERFECTLY IN KEEPING
WITH THE TRIP
WHERE I'VE ALREADY
BEEN RUN DOWN BY ONE
OF YOUR WIENER CARS
AND BEEN STRIP-SEARCHED
AT JOHN F. KENNEDY AIRPORT.
APPARENTLY TO YOU PEOPLE
I LOOK LIKE SOMEONE WHO'S GOT
A BALLOON FULL OF COCAINE
STUFFED UP THEIR BUM.
I-I-I THINK YOU LOOK GREAT.
GOOD NIGHT.
IT WAS VERY NICE
TO MEET YOU ALL.
I'LL GET HER.
PLEASE, HURRY.
SO, DON'T YOU JUST LOVE
THE WAY THEY TALK?
"OOH..." UH, YOU KNOW...
OH!
WHAT?
I THINK THE BABY KICKED.
OH, MY GOD!
( laughs )
OH, NO, WAIT, OH,
THAT WAS THE ELASTIC
IN MY UNDERWEAR BUSTED.
MY GOD! I OVERSLEPT!
I WAS SUPPOSED TO BE ON THE SET
A HALF AN HOUR AGO!
I GOT TO GET OUT OF HERE!
OH, JOEY, YOU
CAN'T GO LIKE THAT.
YOU STINK!
I FELL ASLEEP
BEFORE I COULD TAKE A SHOWER.
THEY'RE JUST TEN BLOCKS AWAY.
IF I RUN, I CAN MAKE IT.
YEAH, RUN TEN BLOCKS.
THAT'LL HELP
THE SMELL.
HEY! OH! SLOW DOWN.
NO, KEEP MOVING.
SO, HOW DID IT GO
WITH JOSHUA LAST NIGHT?
OH, WELL,
I DIDN'T SEE JOSHUA
BUT I DID PUNCH A GIRL
IN THE FACE.
WHAT?
WHY?
IT WAS POURING DOWN RAIN
AND WHEN I GOT THERE, THERE WAS
NO RACHEL GREEN ON THE LIST
BUT THERE WAS A RACHEL "GREEP."
OH, SO DID YOU GET
TO MEET HER?
NO, THERE IS NO RACHEL GREEP
BUT THEN THIS OTHER GIRL
OVERHEARD US
AND SHE WAS ALL,
"I'M RACHEL GREEP!
I'M RACHEL GREEP!"
AND HE LET HER RIGHT IN.
SO YOU HIT HER
IN THE FACE?
NO, SHE WAS ALREADY IN
BUT THEN THIS BIG BITCH
BEHIND ME
TRIED TO STEAL MY UMBRELLA,
SO I CLOCKED HER.
OH! I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS.
ALL I WANTED WAS JUST
A FEW HOURS OUTSIDE OF WORK
TO SEE JOSHUA
SO THAT HE COULD GO AHEAD AND
START FALLING IN LOVE WITH ME.
OH...
PHEEBS.
HONEY, THAT'S YOUR NAME.
THAT'S SHORT FOR PHOEBE?!
I THOUGHT THAT'S
JUST WHAT WE CALLED EACH OTHER.
Monica:
HEY, YOU'RE WEARING PANTS.
THAT'S RIGHT.
WHERE ARE THE GUYS?
I'M READY TO GET DRUNK
AND SEE
SOME STRIPPERS.
IT'S 9:30 IN THE MORNING.
THEY GOT A BREAKFAST BUFFET.
( phone rings )
HELLO? OH, HEY, ROSS.
OOH! LET ME
TALK TO HIM.
OH, MY GOD!
WELL, CAN I JUST...?
SHH! WAIT, WHAT?
SHE'S SHUSHING ME.
SHH! PLEASE!
WHAT'S HE SAYING?
HE'S WITH EMILY AT A BED
AND BREAKFAST IN VERMONT.
WHAT? OH, MY GOD!
WHAT? WHO THE HELL IS EMILY?
NO!
HOW DID THIS HAPPEN?
OW.
HOW-HOW DID HE END UP
IN VERMONT WITH
THAT AWFUL WITCH?
WELL, MAYBE SHE DOESN'T
HIT HIM ALL THE TIME.
Ross:
When we first met her
SHE WAS SOAKING.
HER FEET WERE WET.
WHO WOULDN'T BE MISERABLE?
I'M TELLING YOU, ONCE I GOT HER
INTO A DRY PAIR OF SHOES
SHE WAS
A TOTALLY DIFFERENT PERSON.
ROSS, COME QUICKLY.
A DEER'S OUTSIDE,
EATING FRUIT FROM THE ORCHARD.
THERE'S A DEER
OUTSIDE, EATING FRUIT
FROM THE ORCHARD.
HE HAD TO GO.
THERE WAS A DEER JUST OUTSIDE,
EATING FRUIT
FROM THE ORCHARD.
I DON'T GET THIS.
SHE WAS HORRIBLE.
OKAY, I'M GOING
TO GO STAND OVER THERE.
WHY DO YOU CARE
SO MUCH ANYWAY?
I DON'T CARE.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M JUST UPSET
THAT I'M GETTING NOWHERE
WITH JOSHUA
THAT... YOU KNOW WHAT?
STILL, YOU DO NOT
JUST MEET SOMEONE
AND GO FLITTING OFF
TO VERMONT.
WELL, WHEN YOU FIRST MET BARRY,
YOU FLITTED OFF TO VAIL.
OH, WOULD YOU JUST FOR ONCE
NOT REMEMBER EVERY LITTLE
THING?
SO, YOU KNOW, UH,
WHEN'S HE GETTING BACK?
COUPLE OF DAYS.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I KNEW SOMETHING
LIKE THIS WAS
GOING TO HAPPEN
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
CHANDLER...
YOU CAN'T JUST GO BACK A PHASE.
YES, YOU CAN.
YOU'RE THINKING ABOUT TIME.
YOU CAN'T
GO BACK IN TIME.
LOOK, WHY DON'T YOU JUST...
WHY DON'T YOU DO YOUR PHASE-TWO
STRIP-CLUB THING WITH US?
COME ON,
WE CAN BE GUYS.
( chuckles ):
NO, YOU CAN'T.
COME ON, LET US BE GUYS.
MAYBE WE WANT TO BE GUYS.
YOU DON'T WANT
TO BE GUYS.
YOU'D BE ALL HAIRY,
AND YOU WON'T LIVE AS LONG.
YOU... WOULD YOU JUST
STOP BEING SUCH A WUSS
AND GET THOSE OFF,
AND YOU COME
WITH US AND WATCH NAKED GIRLS
DANCE AROUND!
OKAY.
I'M SORRY.
COME ON.
HEY. JOEY TRIBBIANI.
I'M HERE.
CALM DOWN,
WE GOT TIME.
WE'RE RUNNING
A LITTLE LATE.
OH.
ALL SET.
Joey:
LOOK AT THAT.
CHARLTON HESTON
EATING A LICORICE WHIP.
YEAH, HE LOVES 'EM.
I'VE NEVER SEEN
HIM WITH...
( sniffs )
( both sniffing )
HEY... WHOA...
YEAH, WHAT THE HELL IS THAT?
WHAT SMELLS SO BAD?
YOU.
OH. I COULD SEE
WHY YOU WOULD THINK THAT
BUT, UH...
ACTUALLY, YOU KNOW
WHO I THINK IT IS?
YOU?
NO, NO, IT'S, UH...
IT'S HESTON.
WHAT?
OH, THE MAN REEKS.
SMELLS LIKE HE WENT
ON A THREE-DAY FISHING TRIP
THEN ATE LICORICE.
THERE'S NO WAY HE SMELLS.
HE'S THE ONLY ONE WITH A
SHOWER IN HIS DRESSING ROOM.
REALLY?
A SHOWER, HUH?
AND, UH, WHICH ROOM
MIGHT THAT BE?
THE ONE WITH
"HESTON" ON IT.
INTERESTING.
HEY...
I GOT SOME ONES.
YOU WANT TO PUT THEM
IN HER PANTIES?
NO, THANKS, MOM.
OH, NO, UM, HI.
THAT, THAT...
UM, YOU HAVE
TO PUT THAT OUT
'CAUSE I'M
PREGNANT, SO...
WELL, MAYBE YOU
AND YOUR BABY
OUGHT TO GO
TO ANOTHER STRIP CLUB.
HA-HA, IT'S NOT
MY BABY, HA-HA-HA.
VERY GOOD, YES.
THAT WAS SO GOOD.
REALLY, REALLY ENJOYED IT.
YOU KNOW, VERY EXOTIC.
WELL, I JUST CHECKED
OUR MESSAGES
AND JOSHUA DIDN'T CALL.
YOU WOULD THINK
HE WOULD BE WORRIED
ABOUT ME NOT SHOWING UP
AT HIS CLUB.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT
MAKES IT SO MUCH WORSE?
ROSS IS ALL HAPPY IN VERMONT.
COME ON, LOOK
WHERE YOU ARE.
IF YOU GET A SEC,
ANOTHER ROUND OF DAIQUIRIS.
REMEMBER, UM,
VIRGIN FOR ME, PLEASE.
DON'T LET ME LEAVE
WITHOUT GETTING THE NAME
OF THAT CARPET GUY.
OH, COME ON!
ALL RIGHT,
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M JUST GOING TO GO HOME
AND CALL KATHY.
WELL, IF YOU THINK IT'LL HELP.
NO, THAT WAS A TEST.
IN A COUPLE HOURS, I'LL GET
REALLY DRUNK AND WANT TO CALL.
YOU GUYS HAVE TO STOP ME.
AND THEN AFTER THAT, I'M GOING
TO WANT TO CALL JANICE.
YOU SHOULD. HOW IS SHE?
OH!
I THINK SOMEBODY NEEDS
ANOTHER LAP DANCE.
( imitating pistol firing )
( door slams )
HELLO?
WHO'S IN THERE?
HOW YOU DOING?
WHO IN THE HELL ARE YOU?
UH...
I GUESS YOU WOULDN'T
BELIEVE ME
IF I SAID I WAS
KIRK DOUGLAS, HUH?
PUT SOME PANTS ON, KID,
SO I CAN KICK YOUR BUTT.
NO-NO-NO, NO, NO, WAIT,
YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
SEE, I'M AN ACTOR.
JOEY TRIBBIANI.
I'M DOING A SCENE
WITH YOU TODAY
AND, WELL, I STINK.
YOU'RE IN THIS PICTURE?
YEAH, YEAH.
I'M ONE OF THE COPS
WHO WON'T WORK WITH YOU
'CAUSE YOU'RE A LOOSE CANNON.
ANYWAY, LOOK, I'M REALLY SORRY,
BUT I JUST... I STINK.
JOEY, RIGHT?
YEAH.
COME ON, COME ON.
EVERY ACTOR
AT ONE TIME
OR ANOTHER...
AH!
EVERY ACTOR THINKS HE STINKS.
EVEN LAURENCE OLIVIER
SOMETIMES THOUGHT HE STANK.
BOB REDFORD WON'T EVEN
WATCH HIMSELF.
YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
LISTEN TO ME.
OH, YEAH.
I DON'T KNOW ONE ACTOR
WORTH HIS SALT
WHO ONE TIME IN HIS CAREER
DIDN'T SAY, "GOD, I STINK."
HELL, I JUST DID A SCENE
OUT THERE, FIRST TAKE...
I STUNK THE PLACE UP
BUT...
THE IMPORTANT THING
YOU MUST REMEMBER:
NO MATTER HOW BADLY
YOU THINK YOU STINK
YOU MUST NEVER, EVER BUST
INTO MY DRESSING ROOM
AND USE MY SHOWER.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND ME?
YES, SIR. YES, SIR.
I'M-I'M VERY SORRY.
WAIT A MINUTE.
TAKE YOUR PANTS.
YEAH, OH, YEAH.
( chuckles)
SO, WE DID OKAY
AT THE STRIP CLUB, RIGHT?
OH, YEAH,
THAT WAS GREAT.
THANKS TO YOU
THE HOTTEST COCKTAIL WAITRESS
THERE IS QUITTING
TO TEACH THE
THIRD GRADE.
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
HE STILL HASN'T CALLED.
WHO? JOSH?
IT'S JOSHUA.
HE DOESN'T LIKE "JOSH"?
NO, I DON'T.
ALL RIGHT, WELL,
I'M GOING TO PUT
MY SWEATS BACK ON.
NO, WAIT, WAIT.
OKAY, YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU WERE RIGHT.
WE REALLY WEREN'T
GREAT AT BEING GUYS
BUT DO YOU KNOW WHY?
BECAUSE WE'RE GIRLS.
YEAH?
KNOW WHAT GIRLS
ARE REALLY GOOD AT?
STRIPPING.
NO. LISTENING.
SIT.
YOU KNOW, MAYBE JUST
IT WOULD REALLY, REALLY HELP
IF YOU WOULD JUST TALK.
YEAH, COME ON.
WHAT'S GOING
ON IN THERE?
Monica:
YEAH.
AND, YOU KNOW, IF
YOU WANT TO CRY...
THAT'S OKAY, TOO.
OKAY, LOOK,
I'M GOING TO HAVE TO ASK
YOU ALL TO LEAVE.
COME ON,
CHANDLER.
OH, LOOK, FORGET IT.
WE TRIED, BUT PHASE THREE
IS A LOST CAUSE.
OKAY? THOSE STRIPPERS
WERE INSANELY HOT
AND I COULDN'T PICTURE MYSELF
WITH ANY OF THEM.
( sighs )
THEY REALLY
WERE PRETTY,
WEREN'T THEY?
OH...
OOH...
I REALLY LIKED
THAT FIGHTER PILOT ONE.
OH, CANDY? OH,
SHE WAS SO SPUNKY.
YEAH.
YOU KNOW, I THINK
IF I WERE GOING TO
BE WITH A WOMAN...
IT'D BE WITH SOMEONE
LIKE MICHELLE
BECAUSE SHE WAS...
SHE WAS JUST SO PETITE.
SEE, I DON'T KNOW.
FOR ME IT WOULD HAVE
TO BE CHANTAL.
( gasps )
OH, CHANTAL.
YOU KNOW?
OH, MY GOODNESS. OH...
SHE HAD THE SMOOTHEST SKIN.
I MEAN, WHEN I STUFFED THAT
DOLLAR BILL IN HER G-STRING
AND GRAZED HER THIGH...
PHASE THREE!
I JUST ACHIEVED PHASE THREE!
REALLY?
I AM TOTALLY PICTURING YOU
WITH ALL THOSE WOMEN.
THAT'S... THAT'S
NOT PHASE THREE.
WELL, I'M THERE, TOO.
WELL, ARE WE ALL TOGETHER,
LIKE IN A GROUP?
STOP IT!
YOU'RE KILLING ME!
I THINK I JUST MOVED ON
TO PHASE FOUR.
OH, WHAT IS THAT?
WHAT IS THAT?
WHERE I DON'T WANT
TO HAVE A RELATIONSHIP EVER.
I WANT TO HAVE SEX
WITH STRIPPERS
AND MY FRIENDS.
COME ON.
LET ME SEE THAT SMILE.
I DON'T WANT TO.
PLEASE?
I WANTED TO GO
TO THE STRIP CLUB.
I KNOW, BUT YOU'RE GOING
TO HAVE PLENTY OF CHANCES.
THERE ARE THOUSANDS
OF WOMEN OUT THERE
WHO ARE JUST WAITING
TO SCREW ME OVER.
YEAH, ALL RIGHT.
HEY.
HEY, OH,
HOW WAS VERMONT?
EMILY IS...
INCREDIBLE.
I MEAN, THERE ARE NO WORDS
TO DESCRIBE HER.
THE WHOLE WEEKEND
WAS, WAS LIKE A DREAM.
OH, AND YOU... RACH.
HEY.
YOU WERE SO RIGHT.
WHAT?
WHAT YOU SAID
ABOUT US FINALLY
BEING IN A PLACE
WHERE WE COULD REALLY
BE HAPPY FOR EACH OTHER.
I MEAN, I... I-I ADMIT
I WASN'T QUITE THERE.
YOU KNOW? I MEAN,
THE THOUGHT
OF YOU AND THAT,
THAT JOSH GUY...
JOSHUA.
JOSHUA... GUY...
AT THAT CLUB, DANCING,
HAVING A GOOD TIME.
THE THOUGHT OF
IT KIND OF...
YOU KNOW?
YEAH...
BUT NOW-- BUT NOW
I'M TOTALLY THERE.
I'M FINALLY
WHERE YOU ARE.
OH, THANK GOODNESS.
YEAH, AND... AND
THANK YOU FOR EMILY.
OH, NO PROBLEM.
I'M SO GLAD I COULD HELP.
YOU KNOW, HAPPY FOR YOU.
HAPPY FOR YOU.
OH, NO.
HERE'S WHAT WE'RE GOING TO DO.
YOU ARE GOING
TO TAKE OFF MY CLOTHES;
YOU TWO GO GET THE OILS;
AND YOU JUST CONSTANTLY SCREAM
AT THE TOP OF YOUR VOICE
"CHANDLER'S THE KING!
CHANDLER'S THE KING!"
I WANT TO BE WITH HER.
I LIKE HER.
OH, THAT'S FINE.
GO WITH YOUR INSTINCTS.
WHAT AM I DOING AGAIN?
WOULD YOU PLEASE
PAY ATTENTION?
I COULD WAKE UP
AT ANY MOMENT.
I'M JOSHUA. I'M HERE
TO PICK UP RACHEL.
NO, NO. THAT'S
NOT JOSHUA.
WHAT DO YOU
WANT FROM ME?
I NEVER MET THE GUY.
SO, ANYWAY, RACHEL, I'M
SORRY YOU CAN'T STAY.
THE REST OF US HAVE
A LOT OF WORK TO DO.
[Captioned by
The Caption Center
WGBH Educational Foundation]
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
ALL RIGHT, LISTEN,
I GOT TO WAKE UP.